{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " Where's Jill? She ___ forgotten that we were supposed to meet at 2:00 PM.",
            "a": " would have",
            "b": "  should have",
            "c": "  must have",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I ___ been glad to help you. Why didn't you ask?",
            "a": "  would have",
            "b": "  could have",
            "c": " must have",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " Look! It's raining and Professor Johnson is all wet. He ___forgotten his umbrella again!",
            "a": " should have",
            "b": "  would have",
            "c": "  must have",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ___ turned off the computer when you did! You have caused allkinds of problems!",
            "a": "  shouldn't have",
            "b": " must not have",
            "c": "  might not have",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " She ___ study last night, so she didn't.",
            "a": "  didn't have to",
            "b": " mustn't",
            "c": "  didn't ought to",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " Yes, she ___ been here yesterday. I don't think she was, but Ican't prove that she wasn't.",
            "a": " could",
            "b": "  could have",
            "c": " couldn't have",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I'm not sure where Dave is. He ___ taken Benjamin to a movie or to the zoo.",
            "a": " would have",
            "b": "  may have",
            "c": " ought not to have",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " You shouldn't have driven so fast! You ___ had an accident!",
            "a": " would have",
            "b": "  may have",
            "c": "  might have",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ you speak any foreign languages?",
            "a": " May",
            "b": " Can",
            "c": " Have",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Liz ___ get tired of her jo It is so boring.",
            "a": " has to",
            "b": " must",
            "c": " should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "2",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}